(Raj:)The guy's a genius. Maybe you weren't
challenging enough for him.
(Sheldon:)Not challenging?
I was humiliating the man.
(Sheldon:)I was thinking of writing a book called...
(Sheldon:)...A Brief History of the Time I Made
Stephen Hawking Cry Like a Little Girl.
(Howard:)There's the problem.
You can't beat Hawking like that.
(Howard:)He hates to lose.
Everyone knows the guy's a big baby.
(Howard:)I mean, forget the wheelchair,
he should be in a stroller.
(Penny:)Really?
(Howard:)One time when I was working with him...
(Howard:)...he said that Johnny Depp
was in The Matrix.
(Howard:)I told him he was wrong,
but he kept insisting.
(Howard:)So I looked it up online and showed him.
(Howard:)Well, the next day, he had a pizza party,
and everyone got invited but me.
And then he was all:
"Your invitation
must've gotten lost in the matrix."
(Sheldon:)Good Lord. What have I done?